This is the Blazing Story site, a demo
for a UI component library made for
Blazor.
This library includes components like
buttons, date pickers, radio buttons, and
dropdowns. It also has more
complex ones like steppers.
This blazing story site has a new feature
called the MCP server enabled.
And in this Blazor application project, a
reference to the MCP server is already
set up for GitHub Copilot in Visual
Studio Code.
I have also created custom instructions
for GitHub Copilot to tell it to use the
MCP server from BlazingStory.
Now, let's try a demonstration.
We will give a text prompt and ask GitHub
Copilot to generate a checkout page UI
for an e-commerce site.
I copy the prompt and paste it into the
GitHub Copilot chat window to run it.
You can see that GitHub Copilot is
sending a request to the BlazingStory MCP
server.
Let's wait a moment for it to finish.
It is done.
Let's run it.
Using the demo UI library, it created the
page just as instructed.
You can see that the date picker,
drop-down, and radio button components
are used properly.
The stepper component is also used and
working correctly.
Let's review the generated source code.
Even the input types for the text input
components are chosen correctly.
Next, instead of using a text prompt,
let's try generating from an image.
Here is a rough sketch of a checkout page
made in PowerPoint.
I paste this image into the GitHub
Copilot chat window in Visual StudioCode.
Then, I type a prompt asking it to
generate a page based on the attached
image, and run it.
The generation starts. You can see
that GitHub Copilot is working while
sending requests to the BlazingStory MCP
server. Let's wait a moment again.
It is done.
Let's run it.
Even from an image, it created the page
as instructed using the Demo UI library.
The stepper component is used correctly
and works as expected.
Let's review the generated source code
again.
You can see that the components were
chosen and set up properly, based on the
information from the BlazingStory MCP
server.
As you can see, by using the new MCP
server feature of BlazingStory, we can
generate code that uses the specified UI
component library very accurately.
Thank you for watching!